

GONZALO **LOBO RAMÍREZ**



I am Gonzalo Lobo Ramírez, I am 28 years old with a degree in Finance and Accounting from the University of Seville / SPAIN. The last year of my career I attended the ICESI UNIVERSITY in Colombia. I am also graduate in a Master's Degree in International Trade & Business

I would like to introduce myself as a Junior Full Stack Developer with a great learning capacity. I have experience developing web applications using technologies such as JavaScript,HTML, CSS & frameworks such as React. I also have experience developing back-end applications using languages like Node.js, & frameworks such as Express & Docker.



E-MAIL gonzalolovo@gmail.com

PHONE +34617366953



- HTML5
- GIT
- CSS3
- MONGODB
- JAVASCRIPT
- STYLED-COMPONETS
- TYPESCRIPT
- MUI
- FIREBASE
- NODEJS
- REACT
- POSTGRESOL
- FRAMER-MOTION
- DOCKER



WEBSITE www.gonzalolobocv.vercel.app/

LINKEDIN www.linkedin.com/in/gonzalolr15

GITHUB www.github.com/Macumba45





PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE -

 FREELANCE // Apr 2023 - Today FRONT-END DEVELOPER

I work as a freelance in independent projects to continue learning and training. My job-line is to learn React-native and Swift.

MYHIXEL // Sep 2021 - Oct 2022
INTERNATIONAL LOGISTICS & CUSTOMER SERVICE

Order management, monitoring, incidents, exports and imports in B2C and B2B, inventory and stock management, customer service, incidents, product quality control, e-commerce sales and WhatsApp sales.

 AZCATEC INGENIERIA & TECNOLOGÍA // Apr 2021 - Jul 2021 INTERNATIONAL BUSINESS DEVELOPER

International business developer in an engineering company. My duties are Client Management, International Relationship, Imports and Exports and search for business opportunities



ACADEMIC TRAINING

BOOTCAMP FULL STACK DEVELOPER // Nov 2022 - Apr 2023
BOOTCAMP in The Bridge School

Markup languages: HTML, CSS; Programming languages: JavaScript, TypeScript; Databases: MongoDB, Postgres; Frameworks and libraries: React, Material-UI; Development tools: Git, NodeJS, Docker; Cloud service platforms: Firebase; Other knowledge: Framer.

INTERNATIONAL TRADE & BUSINESS // Nov 2020 - Sep 2021
MASTER IN ESIC - BUSINESS & MARKETING SCHOOL

Master International Trade & Business where i learnt and studied how companies work in the international market, how to export & import also how to internationalization enterpises and analyze the environment where they are.

 FINANCE & ACCOUNTING // Sep 2012 - 2018
UNIVERSITY OF SEVILLE ICESI UNIVERSITY COLOMBIA (EXCHANGE STUDENT)

Student in finance & accounting in the University of Seville. Also ICESI university exchange student last year of my career

HIGH SCHOOL // Ago 2008 - Jun 2009
COVENTRY CHRISTIAN SCHOOL USA

I studied the 1st grade of bachillerato in USA where i learnt USA culture and improved my



ENTREPRENEURSHIP

• **RITUALMOOD** // Mar 2021 - Jul 2021

BUSINESS

Craft project where we made handmade and ritualized candles. Website creation by Shopify, purchases and sales through Alibaba. After-sales customer service. Leaving the project due to lack of time and entry of new projects.

 NAFAS (COLOMBIA) // Ene 2019 - Mar 2020 BUSINESS

Business for the restaurants where the service of Hookahs / hookas was offered in local and nightclubs. Brand, management and sale for own account.

● 2NAIT & EXITAPP // Jun 2015 - 2018 CEO/CMO & CO-FOUNDER

2NAIT is the first online Public Relations. It is an app that offers all the events of nightclubs, parties, specific events, promotions in cocktail bars and offers so that those who enjoy

OTHER DATA OF INTEREST

nightlife can continue to enjoy it in an easier, faster and cheaper way.

- Nautical sports
- Model of photography
- Sport fishing
- Autodidact
- APPS design
- Voluntary Cruz Roja

Find out more about me and my professional skills by scanning this QR code to visit my personal website and see how I can add value to your company.

SCAN ME

